We finished step one,
我们完成了第一步
and will now start with step number two which is finding the output y,
现在开始第二步 找到输出 y
by using the values of h, we just calculated.
利用我们刚刚计算得出的值 h
Since we have more than one output,
由于我们有多个输入
y will be a vector as well.
y 也是向量
We have our initial inputs h,
我们有初始输入 h
and want to find the values of the output y.
我们想要找出输出值 y
Mathematically, the idea is identical to what we just saw in step number one.
从数学角度来说 这个想法相当于我们刚刚在第一步看到的
We now have different inputs.
现在我们有不同的输入
We call them h, and a different weight matrix,
把它们叫做 h 以及另一个权重矩阵
we call it W2.
把它叫做 W2
The output will be vector y.
输出是向量 y
Notice that the weight matrix has three rows,
注意权重矩阵有三行
as we have three neurons in the hidden layer,
因为隐藏层包括 3 个神经元
and two columns, as we have only two outputs.
因为我们只有两个输出 所以有两列
And again, we have a vector by matrix multiplication.
另外我们通过矩阵乘法得到一个向量
Vector h, multiplied by the weight matrix W2,
即向量 h 乘以权重矩阵 W2
gives us the output vector y.
可以得到输出向量 y
We can put it in a simple equation,
我们可以用一个简单方程式表示
where y equals h times W. Once we have the outputs,
即 y = h*W 一旦我们得到输出
we don't necessarily need an activation function.
就不再需要激活函数
In some applications, it can be beneficial to use for example, a softmax function,
在一些应用中 使用例如 Softmax 函数是十分有帮助的
what we call sigma x,
即所谓的 σx
if we want the output values to be between zero and one.
如果我们希望输出值在 0 到 1 之间
You can find more information on this topic in the text after this video.
在看完这个视频后 你可以在下面的文字说明里了解更多关于这个课题的信息
To have a good approximation of the output y,
为了得到输出 y 的充分逼近
we need more than one level of hidden layers.
我们需要不止一个隐藏层
Maybe even 10 or more.
甚至可能需要 10 个或更多
In this picture, I use the general number P. The number
在这幅图中 我使用常规数字 P
of neurons in each layer can change from one layer to the next,
每层神经元的数量各不相同
and as I mentioned before,
正如我之前提到的
can be even thousands.
甚至可能有几千个
Essentially, you can look at these neurons as building
从本质上来说 你看到这些神经元
blocks or lego pieces that can be stacked.
如同堆叠的建筑砖块或乐高积木一样
So how is this done mathematically?
那么如何从数学角度完成这个呢？
Just as before.
与之前一样
A simple vector by matrix multiplication,
通过矩阵乘法得到简单向量
followed by an activation function,
接着利用激活函数
where the vector indicates the inputs,
其中这个向量表示输入
and the matrix indicates the weights connecting one layer to the next.
这个矩阵表示一层连接到下一层的权重
To generalize this model,
为了归纳这个模型
let's look into one random K F layer.
我们观察一个随机的 K F 层
The weight Wij, from the K F layer,
K F 层的权重 Wij
to the K plus one,
和 K+1
corresponds to the I F input,
对应 I F 输入
going into the J F output.
然后得到 J F 输出
You might want to get a pencil for this one,
这里你可能需要用一支笔
as these are important mathematical derivations.
因为这些是重要的数学推导
As you follow the math,
当你进行数学运算时
pause the video, write the derivations in your notes.
暂停视频 在你的注释里写下推导
Try to do so throughout the entire lesson.
在整个课程中尽量这样做
Let's treat layer K,
我们来处理 K 层
as the inputs x and layer K plus one as the outputs of the hidden layer
因为输入 x 和 K+1 层作为隐藏层的输出 h
h. We will have n_x inputs, and m_h outputs.
我们有 n 个输入项 x 和 m 个输出项 h
By the way, if we are not dealing with inputs but
顺便说一句 如果我们面对的不是输入
rather than the outputs of the previous hidden layer,
而是上个隐藏层的输出
the only thing that will change is the letter that we choose to use,
只有我们选择利用的字母才会发生变化
but the calculations will be the same.
不过计算还是一样的
So to make the notation simple,
为了简化符号
let's just stay with x. h1 is the output of an activation function of a sum,
我们还是保留 x h1 是对激活函数求和的输出
where the sum is a multiplication of each input xi,
其中总和是每个输入 xi 乘以
by its corresponding weight component Wi1.
对应的权重 Wi1 的结果
The same way hm is the output of an activation function of a sum,
同样 hm 是对激活函数求和的输出
and the sum is the multiplication of each input xi,
其中总和是每个输入 xi 乘以
by its corresponding weight component Wim.
对应的权重 Wim 的结果
For example, if we have three inputs,
例如有三个输入
and we want to calculate h1,
我们想要计算 h1
it will be the output of an activation function of the following linear combination.
这是线性组合后激活函数的输出
These single element calculations will be helpful in understanding back propagation,
这些单一要素的计算有利于理解反向传播
which is why we want to understand them as well.
这就是我们也要理解它们的原因
But as before, we can also look at
不过与之前一样 我们也会观察
these calculations as a vector by matrix multiplication.
通过矩阵乘法 计算向量
By the way you probably noticed that I didn't emphasize the bias input here.
顺便说一下 你大概也注意到我没有强调这里的偏差输入
The bias does not change any of these calculations.
偏差不会改变这里的任何计算
Simply consider it as a constant input usually one,
简单把它看做常量输入 通常是 1
that is also connected to each of the neurons of the hidden layer by a weight.
也可以通过权重连接到隐藏层的每个神经元
The only difference between the bias and any other input,
偏差和其他输入的唯一差别在于
is the fact that it remains the same as each of the other inputs change.
当其他输入发生变化时 偏差保持不变
And just as all the other inputs,
另外与其他输入一样
the weights connecting it to the next layer are updated as well.
连接输入和下一层的权重也不断更新
So let's stop for a minute.
我们先暂停一下
What is our goal again?
再说一下我们的目标是什么呢？
Our goal is to find the best set of weights,
我们要找到最适合的权重
that will give us at the end the desired output.
能够最后得出理想的输出
Right? At the end,
对不对？ 最后
we want to find a system that will give us the correct output,
我们要找到根据特定输入 得到正确输出的
for a specific input.
系统
In the training phase,
在训练阶段
we actually know the output of a given input.
我们实际上知道特定输入的输出结果
We calculate the output of the system in order to adjust the weights.
我们计算系统的输出 为了调整权重
We do that by finding the error,
通过找出误差 来调整权重
and trying to minimize it.
然后尽量最小化误差
Each iteration of the training phase will decrease the error just a bit,
训练阶段的每次迭代都会一点点降低误差
until we eventually decide that the error is small enough.
直到我们最终确定误差足够小
Let's focus on an intuitive error calculation,
我们重点关注直观误差的计算
which is simply finding the difference between the calculated,
通过计算得出的结果和理想的输出之间的差距
and the desired output.
即可找到区别
This is our basic error.
这是我们的基本误差
For our back propagation calculations,
在我们反向传播计算中
we will use the square error,
我们会使用平方误差
which is also called the loss function.
也叫做损失函数